As sly as a fox, as strong as an ox. As fast as a hare, as brave as a bear. As
free as a bird, as neat as a word. As quiet as a mouse, as big as a house. Oh-Oh-Oh Oh
Oh Oh Oh.. All I want to be...Oh-Oh-Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh.. All I want to be. Oh, Oh Oh..Oh-Oh-Oh
Oh Oh Oh Oh.. All I want to be...is everything. As mean as a wolf, as sharp as a tooth.
As deep as a bite, as dark as the night. As sweet as a song, as right as a wrong.
As long as a road, as ugly as a toad. As pretty as a picture, hanging from a fixture.
Strong like a family, strong as I wanna be. Bright as day, as light as play.
As hard as nails, as grand as a whale. Oh-Oh-Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh.. All I want to be
Oh-Oh-Oh Oh-Oh-Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh.. All I want to be
...is everything, everything at once. Everything at once, Oh-Oh-Oh, everything at
once. As warm as the sun, as silly as fun.
As cool as a tree, a scary as a sea. As hot as fire, cold as ice.
Sweet as sugar, and everything nice. As old as time, as straight as a line.
As royal as a queen, as buzzed as a bee. As stealth as a tiger, smooth as a glider.
Pure as a melody, pure as I want to be. Oh-Oh-Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh.. All I want to be
Oh-Oh-Oh Oh-Oh-Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh.. All I want to be
..is everything...everything at once.